<items>
    <item>
        <key>###H2###</key>
        <val>Marine Club BERRY Booking Form</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Dive Experience###</key>
        <val>Dive Experience</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Water Sports and KAYAK Activity booking###</key>
        <val>Water Sports and KAYAK Activity booking</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Leisure Diving Booking###</key>
        <val>Leisure Diving Booking</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Fill in detail for scuba equipment rental###</key>
        <val>Fill in detail for scuba equipment rental</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###For equipement arrangement###</key>
        <val>For equipement arrangement</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###dives with rental equipment###</key>
        <val>dives with rental equipment</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###dives with own equipment###</key>
        <val>dives with own equipment</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Activity###</key>
        <val>Activity</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Refresh###</key>
        <val>Refresh</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###cancellation dt###</key>
        <val><![CDATA[
            I agree and understand the cancellation policy set by Marine House SEASIR on the official English website link <a href="./cancel.htm" target="_blank">Marine House SEASIR Cancellation Policy</a>If I cancelled on activity day, the cancellation charge will be 100% of full charge.]]></val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###deposit dt 1###</key>
        <val>I will receive a PayPal deposit request from SEASIR LTD. account, to secure your booking please make your deposit of JPY</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###deposit dt 2###</key>
        <val> per person within 3 days start from the day I receive deposit request from our PayPal account, or within 24 hours if the booking request is less than 3 days notice from the departure date. All booking request will cancel if no deposit receive.</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###rest agreement###</key>
        <val><![CDATA[I will have more than 18 hours resting hour after the activity: <span class="underline">Leisure Diving</span>, <span class="underline">Introductory Diving</span>, <span class="underline">Marine Walk</span> before my flight.]]></val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###agreements###</key>
        <val>I’ve READ and AGREED booking policy as below:
    I agree and understand the cancellation policy set by Marine House SEASIR on the official English website link Marine House SEASIR Cancellation Policy. If I cancelled on activity day, the cancellation charge will be 100% of full charge.
    I will have more than 18 hours resting hour from the activity: Leisure Diving, Introductory Diving, Marine Walk before my flight. 
    I will receive a PayPal deposit request from SEASIR LTD. account, to secure your booking please make your deposit of JPY5,000 per person within 3 days start from the day I receive deposit request from our PayPal account, or within 24 hours if the booking request is less than 3 days notice from the departure date. All booking request will cancel if no deposit received.
    I affirm that after checking Marine House SEASIR Health Check List none of us have any question in the Health Check List that answers apply YES to any one of us. I and we agree to accept responsibility for omissions regarding our failure to disclose any existing or past health condition.</val>
    </item>
</items>
