<items>
    <item>
        <key>###H2###</key>
        <val>Cancellation Policy</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Charges###</key>
        <val>Charges</val>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <key>###Non Refundable###</key>
        <val><![CDATA[Non Refundable<br>Deposit Condition]]></val>
    </item>
        <item>
        <key>###Non Refundable dt###</key>
        <val><![CDATA[
<li>If cancellation make less than 14 days from trip date.</li>
<li>If guest NO SHOW on the trip day cause of any reason.</li>
<li>If guest miss boat departure or activity booking time slot.</li>
<li>If guest unable to turn up at designated meeting location and time for any reason.</li>
<li>If the Captain of the boat or Instructor of SEASIR Ltd suspects this individual or group behavior could jeopardize other guest or overall safety measure or the guest under Recreation Drug or Alcohol influence.</li>
<li>Any changes from the original booking cause of the cancellation. This is considering INSUFFICIENT INFORMATION.</li>        
        ]]></val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Deposit Refundable###</key>
        <val><![CDATA[Deposit Refundable<br>Condition]]></val>
    </item>
        <item>
        <key>###Deposit Refundable dt###</key>
        <val><![CDATA[
<li>Deposit refund collection only at SEASIR NAHA BRANCH office or Marine Club BERRY Branch office only.</li>
<li>Trip cancellation by SEASIR Ltd. management due to weather or dangerous sea condition.</li>
        ]]></val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Full Charge###</key>
        <val>Full Charge</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Full Charge dt###</key>
        <val><![CDATA[
<li>Full charge imposed on total cost of the trip if cancellation made less than 24 hour notice from trip date. </li>
<li>Full charge imposed on total cost of the trip if guest unable to turn up at designated meeting location and time for any reason.</li>
<li>Any medical or health conditions are not informed to SEASIR Ltd when booking was made. Please refer to <a href="./health.htm" target="_blank">Marine House SEASIR Health Check List</a> for detail.</li>
        ]]></val>
    </item> 
    <item>
        <key>###Deposit Collection###</key>
        <val>Deposit Collection</val>
    </item>    
    <item>
        <key>###Deposit Collection dt###</key>
        <val><![CDATA[
<li>SEASIR NAHA branch full day activity JPY5,000 per person.</li>
<li>SEASIR NAHA half day activity JPY3,000 per person.</li>
<li>SEASIR AKA Branch accomodation and any activity JPY5,000 per person.</li>
<li>Marine Club BERRY all activity and Paintball JPY4,000 per person.</li>
<li>PADI diving course booking JPY5,000 per person</li>
<li>Whale Watching Excursion Trip by SEASIR NAHA Branch JPY2,000 per person.</li>
        ]]></val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Notice###</key>
        <val>Notice</val>
    </item>     
    <item>
        <key>###Notice dt###</key>
        <val><![CDATA[
<li>Please do fill in or inform our office at least 24 hours in advance if there is any special request such as vegetarian food or any allegy of certain food when making online or by phone booking, or standard meal will be provided as usual.</li>
<li>Only guest are register in the booking form are allow to participate or in the boat on the day.</li>
<li>SEASIR Ltd. hold all rignts of any changes of price or activty location due to safety and management decision.</li>
        ]]></val>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <key>###extra li###</key>
        <val><![CDATA[
<li><span class="seasir-red">Marine House SEASIR</span> and <span class="berry-pink">Marine Club BERRY </span> holds all rights to cancel trip due to weather concern and safety</li>
<li><span class="seasir-red">Marine House SEASIR</span> and <span class="berry-pink">Marine Club BERRY </span>holds all right to refuse the guest to onboard if suspected there is any behavior problem of this guest due to overall safety concern.</li>
<li>All cancellation charges are imposed based on total cost of trip.</li>
            ]]></val>
    </item>
</items>
