<items>
    <!-- {{{ header -->
    <item>
        <key>###headTitle###</key>
        <val>Okinawa Water Sports Center – Marine Club BERRY Paintball</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###headDesc###</key>
        <val>Okinawa water sports center provide English, Mandarin and Cantonese speaking marine staff</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###headKeywords###</key>
        <val>Okinawa,Water,Sports,Banana,Boat,Jet,Ski,Kayak,Scuba,Diving,Snorkeling,English,Foreign,Paintball</val>
    </item>
    <!-- }}} header -->
    <item>
        <key>###theTeam###</key>
        <val>Berry Paintball</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###theTeamIntro###</key>
        <val><![CDATA[From 2014 Berry have started this Paintball activity in Kanucha Bay Hotel &Villas Nago with a soft opening. This paintball do come with many customise game that do suit for Family, Group of friends and Company Outdoor program. Is a very highly recommended team work field game that we put people together in a team. Beside for group field game, Berry do have some customize game for family purpose. ]]></val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Own Preparation###</key>
        <val>Own Preparation</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Own Preparation dt###</key>
        <val><![CDATA[
            <li>Wearing long sleeve shirt and pants during the game (Jeans and tick material top require)</li>
            <li>Extra set of wear to change after Paintball game (shower and towel provided)</li>
            <li>Sport shoe or any outdoor purpose sneaker (must full cover your foot)</li>
            <li>A small towel use during the game.</li>
            ]]></val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###paintball note###</key>
        <val>Guest will not allow to participate painball activity on the spot is suspected under Recreation Drug or Alcohol influence (full charges will still apply)</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Plan###</key>
        <val>Plan</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Duration###</key>
        <val>Duration</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Minimum Pax###</key>
        <val>Minimum Pax</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Paintball###</key>
        <val>Paintball</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Price Per Person###</key>
        <val>Price Per Person</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Basic Plan###</key>
        <val>Basic Plan</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Advance Plan###</key>
        <val>Advance Plan</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Group###</key>
        <val>Group(Charter)</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Extra Paintball###</key>
        <val>Extra Paintball</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###hour###</key>
        <val>hour</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###hours###</key>
        <val>hours</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###minutes###</key>
        <val>minutes</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###pax###</key>
        <val>pax</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###each###</key>
        <val>each</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###paintball###</key>
        <val>paintball</val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Booking procedure dt###</key>
        <val><![CDATA[Click on <span class="booking-blue">BOOKING NOW</span>, you will require to fill in your email address as your contact. Fill in all information as required and summit. You will receive a PayPal deposit request from SEASIR LTD. account, to secure your booking please make your deposit of JPY4,000 per person within 3 days start from the day you receive deposit request from our PayPal account, or within 24 hours if your booking request is less than less than 3 days from the departure date. All booking request will cancel if no deposit receive.]]></val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key></key>
        <val></val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key></key>
        <val></val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key></key>
        <val></val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key></key>
        <val></val>
    </item>
    <item>
        <key>###Paintball Addr###</key>
        <val>156-2 Abu, Nago, Okinawa 905-2263, JAPAN</val>
    </item>
</items>

